{
    "Maths": [
        {
            "question_number": 21,
            "question": "Let P be the image of the point Q(7, −2, 5) in the line L : (x−1)/2 = (y+1)/3 = (z−5)/4 and R(5, p, q) be a point on L. Then the square of the area of △PQR is .",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "957"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 22,
            "question": "If ∫ (x²+x+9)/√(x²+x+1) dx = x√(x² + x + 1) + α√(x² + x + 1) + β loge |x + 1/2 + √(x² + x + 1)| + C, where C is the constant of integration, then α + 2β is equal to ....",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "16"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 23,
            "question": "Let y = y(x) be the solution of the differential equation 2 cos x dy/dx + y sin 2x = 4y sin x, x ∈ (0, π/2). If y(π/3) = 0, then y'(π/3) + y(π/3) is equal to .",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 24,
            "question": "Number of functions f : {1, 2, . . .,100} → {0, 1}, that assign 1 to exactly one of the positive integers less than or equal to 98, is equal to .",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "392"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 25,
            "question": "Let H₁: x²/a² − y²/b² = 1 and H₂ : x²/A² − y²/B² = 1 be two hyperbolas having length of latus rectums 15√2 and 12√5 respectively. Let their ecentricities be e₁ = √5/2 and e₂ respectively. If the product of the lengths of their transverse axes is 100√10, then 25e₂² is equal to .",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "55"
        }
    ],
    "Physics": [
        {
            "question_number": 46,
            "question": "The ratio of the power of a light source S₁ to that the light source S₂ is 2. S₁ is emitting 2 × 10¹⁵ photons per second at 600 nm . If the wavelength of the source S₂ is 300 nm, then the number of photons per second emitted by S₂ is . . . . . . ×10¹⁴.",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 47,
            "question": "A string of length L is fixed at one end and carries a mass of M at the other end. The mass makes (1/π) rotations per second about the vertical axis passing through end of the string as shown. The tension in the string is . . . . . . ML.",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "36"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 48,
            "question": "The increase in pressure required to decrease the volume of a water sample by 0.2% is P × 10⁵Nm⁻². Bulk modulus of water is 2.15 × 10⁹Nm⁻². The value of P is . . . . . .",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "43"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 49,
            "question": "A tightly wound long solenoid carries a current of 1.5 A . An electron is executing uniform circular motion inside the solenoid with a time period of 75 ns. The number of turns per metre in the solenoid is . . . . . . -.",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "250"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 50,
            "question": "Acceleration due to gravity on the surface of earth is ' g'. If the diameter of earth is reduced to one third of its original value and mass remains unchanged, then the acceleration due to gravity on the surface of the earth is . . . . . . g.",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "9"
        }
    ],
    "Chemistry": [
        {
            "question_number": 58,
            "question": "For the reaction, H₂(g) + I₂(g) ⇌ 2HI(g) Attainment of equillibrium is predicted correctly by :",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 65,
            "question": "The structure of the major product formed in the following reaction is :",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 71,
            "question": "In Carius method of estimation of halogen, 0.25 g of an organic compound gave 0.15 g of silver bromide (AgBr). The percentage of Bromine in the organic compound is . . . . . . ×10⁻¹% (Nearest integer). (Given : Molar mass of Ag is 108 and Br is 80 g mol⁻¹)",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "255"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 72,
            "question": "The observed and normal molar masses of compound MX₂ are 65.6 and 164 respectively. The percent degree of ionisation of MX₂ is . . . . . . %. (Nearest integer)",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "75"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 73,
            "question": "Consider a complex reaction taking place in three steps with rate constants k₁, k₂ and k₃ respectively. The overall rate constant k is given by the expression k = √(k₁k₂)/k₃. If the activation energies of the three steps are 60,30 and 10 kJ mol⁻¹ respectively, then the overall energy of activation in kJmol⁻¹ is ....... (Nearest integer)",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "20"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 74,
            "question": "The possible number of stereoisomers for 5-phenylpent-4-en-2-ol is . . . . . .",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 75,
            "question": "The hydrocarbon (X) with molar mass 80 g mol⁻¹ and 90% carbon has . . . . . . degree of unsaturation.",
            "options": [],
            "answer": "3"
        }
    ]
}